{
    "id": "c7a7628337034c6a8a70908cb53a3f22",
    "title": "Subject-Verb Agreement",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Plutarch’s Lives ……………. an interesting book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The United States ………………… one of the most influential countries in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Thousand dollars …………… a huge sum.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Either you or I ………………. mistaken.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "am",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader, as well has his followers, …………… arrested.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Wool, as well as cotton, ………………… exported from India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No news ……………… good news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The king, with his ministers, …………….. coming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Time and tide ………………. for none.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "waits",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The state of his affairs …………….. a cause for concern.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}